Hello everyone welcome and welcome back to my
channel, so the product we are going to talk about today is
epidermal cleansing lotion, so
whatever product I upload on my YouTube
channel, it is of the same quality, so let's talk about
its ingredients,
it has three types of minerals like
saturated alcohol which softens our
skin, one coma three saturated
glycol which moisturizes and smoothes
our skin and thirdly sodium lauryl
sarsonite, so it can be used
for dry, sensitive and irritated skin, it is very good and it
also cures sunburn well, let's talk about
its price, it is available for Rs. 339,
we get it online for Rs. 125 and its
current price is Rs.
399 and for details you
can check the description, it
cannot be said, so thank you, so keep
watching this video on match